[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "What do you make out jury so far out three and a bit hours asking for a lot of documentation, clearly prepared to go through a lot of evidence, it would seem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, Piers, what I think is going on is they are looking the evidence and we've always believed if they looked at the evidence, that they will hold George Zimmerman accountable for killing an unarmed teenager.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Trayvon"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Because it was clearly trying to create an impression to the jury that Trayvon Martin wasn't just a kid, he was a quite strapping teenager?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, what is interesting about that, Piers, it was extremely emotional, especially for Trayvon's mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark O'Mara"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "But isn't that exactly what George Zimmerman did that night when he profiled and made assumptions about Trayvon Martin and was wrong and, unfortunately, Trayvon had to pay with his life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "There was a moment Mark O'Mara turned his attention to you personally.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "Trayvon Martin", "Trayvon"], "TIME": ["that night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump", "Ben Crump"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you think George Zimmerman would have even been charged had Ben Crump not been pulled into this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "No, Ben Crump or someone like him, because had Ben Crump not gotten involved in the case, maybe for some good reasons to begin with.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "Ben Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Ben Crump, your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, Piers, you know, they seem to forget that Trayvon Martin was a dead, unarmed kid on the ground who his client profiled, followed, pursued, and shot in the heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I will say it like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "If Trayvon Martin was in the car and profiled and followed and pursued George Zimmerman and killed him, what would the verdict be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Ben Crump, always good to talk to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "When you hear Ben Crump talked like that, it's very hard to see how this jury can basically say to George Zimmerman, I think, off you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Yes, I think they're going to be focused on facts, obviously, their own biases, their own interpretations and their emotions are going to weigh into that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont Hill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Just any human level, isn't that going to be incredibly powerful with an all-female, mother- related jury?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "It's going to be powerful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Crump"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, I take issues with one of the points that Mr. Crump made.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Is this a fuss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Well, I will tell you -- one of the things I think come from this very tragic situation and I think regardless of where people sort out of what will happen, I think that we all agree that there is a tragedy this 17-year-old lost his life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "I look at what's happened with gun control in America, where absolutely zero happened after Sandy Hook and Aurora, why should I have confidence anything will change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "CD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Personally, I think stand your ground is a terrible, terrible law.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandy Hook"], "LOCATION": ["America", "Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "It's a license to kill people, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I think it's an awful law.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What is that, when a grown man frustrated, angry with hate in his heart gets out of his car with a loaded gun and follows a child, a stranger in the dark, and shoots him through his heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "He's not guilty of anything but protecting his own life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", ",", "IN", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Six women, five mothers, five white mothers, women, what difference will that make do you think to the dynamic in that jury room, if anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, I think it will make a difference -- if you look at your show over the past couple weeks, when you've had multiple women on, that have disagreement about particular topic, you can see how animated they get.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "I'm also sure -- although they won't be aware of the huge attention the trial is getting on television -- they will be aware, I'm sure, before that this was potentially going to be a big story, wouldn't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Of course, they are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 266, "question": "I thought it was interesting with the use of force expert who -- the prosecution was cross examining him, said if Zimmerman is being straddled by Trayvon Martin, how easy would it be for him to get the gun out of his waist belt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Let me come to Jeff --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman", "Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Jeff, the point you were going to make?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, the defense is that he got out of the car and then he was just assaulted.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Did you believe his story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I actually did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "I mean, if he's been -- if he's been taught this, then to leave the car is beyond his training and you got to wonder, if those jurors are thinking what happened that he actually left that car to go after Trayvon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Why did you believe that so strongly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "You take into consideration everything you learn about an individual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Surely, there is another option than pulling out a gun and shooting him dead, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "The main concern that you have is everybody makes the presumption that it's just a 17-year-old kid walking home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Judge Hatchett?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "That's the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Hatchett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I believe Zimmerman is guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Charles Blow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I think that to me is the most crucial point about what the public outcry was here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "So, my question is, can the jury be truly objective?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Daniel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Thanks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 481, "question": "I'm around the same age as Trayvon, and would this case be different if it was me that night instead of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "See, this is a great question --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Can I answer it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "No, you had your chance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "If Trayvon had been that young man, Daniel, would we be even debating this here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "We might be debating parts of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "But you were not in Zimmerman's castle, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "It doesn't matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "It would make it all so much easier, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJR", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yes, it would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Is that normally how these things work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "It can fluctuate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Do you think it was a deliberate strategy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "To say, how could this guy so out of shape, he could never win a fight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I don't think -- a lot of people have said that to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "What do you think is going to come back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "What do you think is the fair result?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "From what I've seen, it depends on how they take Zimmerman's test -- he didn't testify, but his statements that are in part of the evidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "CC", "JJS", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 599, "question": "What do you personally think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I believe that it is hard to buy his account of what happened, particularly and most importantly --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Judge Hatchett, very quickly, your verdict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I think it's going to be manslaughter, and I think it will come early next week.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Hatchett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Judge Alex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I think legally, it's an acquittal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Marc?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "If I were a juror, I would say not guilty based on what I seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]